lensdiaries.com 2016-05-25

# Privacy Statement | Lens Diaries™

**Privacy Statement**

 **

LensDiaries.com Website Privacy Statement

**

**This document was last updated on June 23, 2013.**

**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS** LensDiaries.com and it’s owners is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing LensDiaries.com and it’s owners, you acknowledge and fully understand LensDiaries.com and it’s owners’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

**PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES** Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in LensDiaries.com and it’s owners services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT** LensDiaries.com and it’s owners collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies. 

Web Server Logs. When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

Your Internet protocol address.

The kind of browser or computer you use.

Number of links you click within the site.

State or country from which you accessed the site.

Date and time of your visit.

Name of your Internet service provider.

Web page you linked to our site from.

Pages you viewed on the site.

**Use of Cookies** LensDiaries.com and it’s owners may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. LensDiaries.com and it’s owners reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into LensDiaries.com, a site that relies on third-party cookies). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

**Personal Information Users** Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

To fulfill your service requests for services.

To protect ourselves from liability,

To respond to legal process or comply with law, or

In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES** LensDiaries.com web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow LensDiaries.com and it’s owners to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. LensDiaries.com and it’s owners may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. LensDiaries.com and it’s owners prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

**ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION** We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant –Contact Us

**CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT** LensDiaries.com and it’s owners has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**CONTACTING US** If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please [Contact Us](http://www.lensdiaries.com/contact/) or send your comments to:

LensDiaries.com  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel  
2307 Trinity Pass  
San Antonio, Texas 78261 

By Email:

**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF OUR EMAIL POLICIES** LensDiaries.com respects your privacy. Any and all personal information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed without your permission. Any information gathered by us will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to let us know. Resale or disclosure of information to third parties: LensDiaries.com does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms without your approval. Any email address information sold or rented to third parties will only be through opt-in approval by the user or member. Should such information be sold or rented, the buyer does not see the actual names, only a safeguareded list. No user’s information will be sold or rented for spamming purposes. A user may opt-out at any time–instantly–by logging into their account, then going to “Settings” then “Manage Account” and deleting their listings. If user has any problems, they may contact us and ask us for removal of their account by merely clicking any “[Contact Us](http://www.lensdiaries.com/contact/)” link.

If a user or member wishes not to receive any emails from the administrator, the LensDiaries.com updates, and/or any type of LensDiaries.com newsletters, then they must delete their entire account. Part of the joining this site requires that you opt-in to our administrative and LensDiaries.com updates and/or any type of newsletters we may send. Please keep in mind, we do not like spam and we adhere to the CAN-SPAM act. We do our best to minimize any administrative or LensDiaries.com emails to our users, but in order to contact you from time to time, we must have the ability to email you personally. Again, we do not spam nor believe in it! 

Privacy of our email lists: LensDiaries.com does not provide the actual email addresses when a list is sold or rented. All members of any lists owned by LensDiaries.com. agreed to join our list before being accepted and can opt-out without any questions or reasons according to the guidelines provide above under our privacy policy and options, 100% and instantly, at any time. None of our lists are sold or rented to any type of spam or spam services. LensDiaries.com supports all anti-spamming legislation and existing laws. If you have any questions, [please contact us](http://www.lensdiaries.com/contact/).

Welcome to LensDiaries.com (Lens Diaries™), a hybrid photography blog with social flair. The photoblog provides photo tips, photo tutorials and photo diaries by professional photographer, author, writer, speaker and social media consultant, Rolando Gomez. 

Lens Diaries™ is open to all levels of photographers, beginners to advanced, including fine art photography, fashion photography, wedding photography, portrait photography, people photography, baby photography, sports photography, nature photography, iphoneography, landscape photography, studio photography, underwater photography, etc. 

Our primary photography focus is digital photography and digital cameras. From iPhones to Canon’s and Nikon’s, you can count on us!
